question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Faust is a playable character in 'Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator'.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails' real name is Miles Prower.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is referred to as 'The Shape'.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Watch Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }
]
